<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GamePlan</string>

    <string name="Terms">
    <![CDATA[
    <h2>Welcome to GamePlan!</h2>
    <p>Congratulations, you’ve just found the best app for planning your gaming sessions and ensuring that nobody chickens out at the last minute (well, we try). Before diving into endless button mashing and leaderboard domination, please read these terms and conditions—at least skim them, we’re not your parents.</p>
    <br>
    <h3>Acceptance of Terms</h3>
    <p>By using GamePlan, you agree to the following:</p>
    <p><strong>You acknowledge</strong> that reading this entire document is optional, but ignoring it means you’re legally obligated to forgive us for any glitches, crashes, or general nonsense the app might throw your way.</p>
    <p><strong>You won’t sue us</strong> if your carefully planned game night dissolves into chaos when Nathan brings up that one time you rage quit <em>Mario Kart</em>.</p>
    <p><strong>We can change these terms</strong> whenever we want, even if it’s just to add more jokes or clarify that <u>Monopoly</u> is a friendship-ending experience.</p>
    <br>
    <h3>User Responsibilities</h3>
    <p>As a proud user of GamePlan, here are your sacred duties:</p>
    <p><strong>Thou shalt not ghost</strong> your friends after RSVPing to a game night. <small>Seriously, we see you.</small></p>
    <p><strong>Thou shalt always respect</strong> the sacred rule of "No spoilers, no rage-quitting, and no cheating (unless it’s hilarious)."</p>
    <p>If you plan a game night involving over <strong>12 people</strong>, GamePlan suggests snacks, a seating plan, and possibly a referee.</p>
    <p><u>Do not</u>, under any circumstances, use this app to schedule a gaming session during your significant other’s birthday dinner. <strong>We cannot and will not cover for you.</strong></p>
    <br>
    <h3>App Usage</h3>
    <p>GamePlan is here to help you manage your game library and coordinate sessions, not solve your existential crises about whether you’re a better healer or DPS player.</p>
    <p>We make no guarantees that using GamePlan will improve your game skills, fix your internet connection, or stop Greg from hogging the best loot.</p>
    <p>Expect occasional bugs, because this is software, and bugs are like NPCs in a Bethesda game—you can’t avoid them forever.</p>
    <p>If you find a particularly hilarious bug, please report it. <i>Bonus points if you send us a meme about it.</i></p>
    <br>
    <h3>Intellectual Property</h3>
    <p>Everything in GamePlan belongs to us, including the questionable UI decisions and the witty text you’re reading right now.</p>
    <p><strong>Don’t steal our code or graphics</strong> unless you enjoy conversations that begin with "You’ve been served."</p>
    <br>
    <h3>Data Collection</h3>
    <p>We don’t collect personal data right now, but if we did, it would be securely stored and definitely not labeled <tt>PasswordzLOL</tt>.</p>
    <p>If we ever decide to collect data, we promise to tell you <small>(unless it’s just asking what your favorite pizza topping is).</small></p>
    <br>
    <h3>Liability Limitations</h3>
    <p>We are not responsible for the following:</p>
    <p><strong>Lost friendships</strong> due to gaming-related betrayals.</p>
    <p><strong>Accidental late-night gaming sessions</strong> that cause you to miss work or class.</p>
    <p><strong>Arguments over whether Dark Souls</strong> is too hard or just a "learning experience."</p>
    <p>Use GamePlan at your own risk. We suggest having snacks on hand to soften the blow when someone picks <u>Rainbow Road</u>.</p>
    <br>
    <h3>Updates and Changes</h3>
    <p>We reserve the right to update these terms whenever we feel like it—possibly after an all-nighter fueled by pizza and regret.</p>
    <p>We might not tell you about these changes, but rest assured, they’ll always be for the greater good <small>(probably).</small></p>
    <br>
    <h3>Contact</h3>
    <p>Need help? Have questions? Want to suggest a feature that makes your cat the ultimate game night mascot?</p>
    <p>Contact us at <a href="mailto:fakeemail@gameplan.com">fakeemail@gameplan.com</a>. Or send a carrier pigeon. <i>We respect the classics.</i></p>
    <br>
    <h3>Bonus Rules for a Better Gaming Experience</h3>
    <p><strong>Always charge your controller</strong> before game night. Nobody likes waiting for a firmware update.</p>
    <p>If you lose, remember <strong>it’s just a game</strong> <small>(unless you’re winning, in which case bragging is encouraged).</small></p>
    <p>Never underestimate the power of snacks. <strong>A well-fed gamer is a happy gamer.</strong></p>
    <p>In the event of a tie, we suggest <em>rock-paper-scissors</em> or <i>dramatic storytelling</i> to determine the winner.</p>
    <br>
    <h3>Final Thoughts</h3>
    <p>Thanks for choosing GamePlan! We hope your game nights are legendary, your loot drops are epic, and your friends never forget to RSVP. And remember, if things go terribly wrong—<strong>blame Nathan.</strong></p>
    ]]>
</string>


</resources>